{
    "subject": "resource/The_Royal_Oui",
    "predicate": "ontology/background",
    "object": "group_or_band",
    "human_readable": "The background of The Royal Oui is a group or band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9299106001853943,
            "question": "Is The Royal Oui a solo artist or a group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6980604529380798,
            "question": "Are there any famous members of The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6757041215896606,
            "question": "What is The Royal Oui known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6296464204788208,
            "question": "Where is The Royal Oui based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6065906286239624,
            "question": "What genre of music does The Royal Oui play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5817281007766724,
            "question": "What type of entity is The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5519816875457764,
            "question": "Where can people listen to The Royal Oui's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46278882026672363,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by The Royal Oui?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43803662061691284,
            "question": "Has The Royal Oui released any albums or singles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24335989356040955,
            "question": "Has The Royal Oui won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The background of The Royal Oui is a group or band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_273_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has The Royal Oui released any albums or singles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_273_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular songs by The Royal Oui?",
            "html": "dbpedia_273_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can people listen to The Royal Oui's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_273_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_273_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about The Royal Oui, describing them as a husband and wife singer-songwriter duo. This supports the statement that The Royal Oui is indeed a group or band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}